const qAndA = [
    {question: "which coutry hosted the 2019 African cup of Nations",
     option: ["kenya", "zimbabwe", "Egypt", "Ghana"],
     answer: "Egypt"},

     {question: "How many teams participated in the 2019 African cup of Nations",
     option: ["21", "22", "26", "24"],
     answer: "24"},

     {question: "which team won 4th place in the 2019 African cup of Nations",
     option: ["Gambia", "Tunisia", "south Africa", "Ghana"],
     answer: "Tunisia"},

     {question: "which coutry hosted the 2019 African cup of Nations",
     option: ["kenya", "zimbabwe", "Egypt", "Ghana"],
     answer: "Egypt"},

     {question: "who was the top scorer in the 2019 African cup of Nations",
     option: ["Odion ighalo", "Mohammed salah", "Rais M'Bolhi", "Donnald trump"],
     answer: "Odion ighalo"},

     {question: "who got the award for best player in  the 2019 African cup of Nations",
     option: ["Mikel Obi", "Ismael Bennacer", "Farouk Johnson", "kieta lambert"],
     answer: "Ismael Bennacer"},

     {question: "which won the award for the best young player in the 2019 African cup of Nations",
     option: ["kreplin Diatta", "chukwueze Andrew ", "Effiong samuel", "Victor smith"],
     answer: "kreplin Diatta"},

     {question: "How much was the final position prize money in the 2019 African cup of Nations",
     option: ["$4.5million", "$5.2million", "$3.5million", "$4.7million"],
     answer: "$4.5million"},

     {question: "who was the major the sponsor for the 2019 African cup of Nations",
     option: ["Visa", "1XBET", "Total", "Yamaha"],
     answer: "Total"},

     {question: "what was the official mascot of the 2019 African cup of Nations",
     option: ["vuvuzela", "wolf", "Bear", "Tut"],
     answer: "Tut"},]





















